

ROSEMARIE HALIM

Graphic Designer

Phone: +1 519 991 5604

Email: rosemarie.m.halim@gmail.com *Website:* www.rosemariehalim.ca

Rose believes in strong team work to create an experience for clients by creating new and unique graphic solutions. She enjoys all parts of the creative process and learning new skills and is not afraid to take initiative and take on new challenges to improve herself. Her goal is to have fun and spread new ideas and perspectives around our community.

SKILLS

PROFESSIONAL

- Web Design
- · Graphic Design
- Corporate Branding
- · Package Design
- UI / UX
- Illustration

EDUCATION

GRAPHIC DESIGNST. CLAIRE COLLEGE

2017 - 2020

2022

FULL STACKCARLETON UNIVERSITY

EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER | FREELANCE

2018 - PRESENT

As a freelance designer, Rose provides a wide variety of services, ranging from web design to branding to print.

- Ensures attention to detail in all design work.
- Follows current visual design trends and applies to designs.
- Organizes meetings with clients and prioritizes client satisfaction.

JR GRAPHIC DESIGNER | DAVID J DUKE CREATIVE DESIGN STUDIO 2019 – 2020

David Jacob Duke Creative Design Studio is a multi-functional creative studio based in Windsor, Ontario.

- Designed vendor banners and social media posts for 2019 Windsor Comicon.
- Created and designed logos, posters, and ads for clients.
- Prioritized collaboration with team to meet client needs.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER | HIT POINT PRESS

2021 - 2022

Hit Point Press is a small, Canadian company passionate about bringing players compelling miniatures, gaming accessories, and campaigns for their tables.

- Created and designed booklets for monthly subscriptions.
- Posted social media posts revolving around monthly subscriptions.
- Received and implemented feedback from the team to refine designs and deliver quality work.



ROSEMARIE HALIM

Graphic Designer

EXPERTISE

TECHNICAL

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe XD
- Visual Studio
- Indesign
- Figma
- CSS
- HTML
- JavaScript

INTERESTS

HOBBIES

- Coffee
- Travel
- Music
- Video Games

EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)

GRAPHIC DESIGNER & PRINTER | MUCCI FARMS

2019 - 2020

Mucci Farms is a grower, packer, shipper and marketer of fresh flavourful greenhouse grown produce.

- Created and designed displays, labels, and packaging.
- Collaborated with the team to create trade show booths and displays.
- Adapted to fast-paced work environments, managing multiple projects and tight deadlines

REFERENCES

DAVID J DUKE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

E: info@davidjacobduke.com

WAYNE ST. DENIS

CREATIVE DESIGN MANAGER

E: wstdenis@muccifarms.com

JENNA PETERS BRAND PROMOTIONS MANAGER

E: jpeters@muccifarms.com

JAMES CUBELO

MARKETING SAMPLE COORDINATOR

E: jcubelo@muccifarms.com